Department of Computer Science Technical Reports 1985-1995: Finding Aid
Engineering Library
Department of Computer Science Technical Reports
1985-1995
(ST) QA75.5.T725
ENG0001
Princeton University. Library Engineering Library Friend Center for Engineering Education Princeton, NJ, 08540 609-258-3200 englib@princeton.edu
1.0 linear feet 340 volumes
Princeton University. Department of Computer Science.
Consists of technical reports created by the Department of Computer Science at Princeton University between 1985 and 1995.
Consists of technical reports from the Department of Computer Science.
Collection is open for research use.
Electronic data processing.; Electronic digital computers.; Machine theory.; Princeton University
- Mutual Exclusion in Partitioned Distributed Systems, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-001-85; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Database Processing with Triple Modular Redundancy, 1985; Report No.CS-TR-002-84; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Pittelli, Frank; 1 item
- Rotation Distance, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-003-85; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Thurston, William P.; 1 item
- A Locally Adaptive Data Compression Scheme, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-004-85; Bentley, Jon Louis; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Wei, Victor K.; 1 item
- Planar Point Location Using Persistent Search Trees, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-005-85; Sarnak, Neil; 1 item
- Efficient Top-Down Updating of Red-Black Trees, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-006-85; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Rectilinear Planar Layouts of Planar Graphs and Bipolar Orientations, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-007-85; Rosenstiehl, Pierre; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- The Pairing Heap: A New Form of Self-Adjusting Heap, 1985 July; Report No. CS-TR-85; Sedgewick, Robert; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Policies for Dynamic Vote Reassignment, 1985; Report No. CS-010-85; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- Using Semantic Knowledge for Transaction Processing, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-009-85; Cordon, Ricardo A.; 1 item
- A Proposed Architecture for a Massive Memory Machine, 1985 October; Report No. TR-CS-011; Lopresti, Daniel; 1 item
- Optimizing Shadow Recovery Algorithms, 1985 October; Report No. TR-CS-012; Kent, Jack; 1 item
- Two Streamlined Depth-First Search Algorithms, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-013-86; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Geometric Complexity and Computer Graphics - Does Theory Apply in Practice?, 1985; Report No.CS-TR-014-85; Dobkin, David P.; 1 item
- Embedding Computation in One-Dimensional Automata by Phase Coding Solitons, 1985; Report No. CS-TR-015-85; Kamal, Irfan; Steiglitz, Kenneth; Watson, Arthur; 1 item
- An Example of Structured Explanation Generation, 1985 November; Report No. CS-TR-016-85; Bienkowski, M.A.; 1 item
- Design of Interleaved Massive Memory Machine, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-017-85; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- A Load Balancing Implementation for a Local Area Network of Workstations, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-018-86; Alfonso, Rafael; Goldman, Phillip; Potrebic, Peter; 1 item
- Superposed Parallel Buses: A Systolic Area-time Optimal VLSI Interconnection, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-019-86; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- The Total DNA Homology Experiment, 1986 January; Report No.CS-TR-020-86; Welsh, J. Douglas; 1 item
- The Rotation Graph of Binary Trees is Hamiltonian, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-021-86; Lucas, Joan; 1 item
- Using Residue Arithmetic to Simplify VLSI Processor Arrays for Dynamic Programming, 1986; Report No. TR-CS-022-86; Lipton, Richard J.; Lopresti, Daniel; 1 item
- Permutations on Superposed Parallel Buses, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-024-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- A Weinberger Array Generator, 1986 January; Report No.CS-TR-023-86; La Paugh, Andrea; Lin, William W; Yeh, Susan S.; 1 item
- Intersection of Convex Objects in Two and Three Dimensions, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-025-86; Chazelle, B.; Dobkin, David P.; 1 item
- Practical Variations of Shellsort, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-02-86; Incerpi, Janet; Sedgewick, Robert; 1 item
- Reliable Scheduling in a TMR Database System, 1986 April; Report No. CS-TR-028-86; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Pittelli, Frank; 1 item
- Distributed Computing Research at Princeton-1985, Report No.CS-TR-029-85; Abbott, Robert; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Cordon, Ricardo A.; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Goldman, Phillip; Karol, Mark; Kent, Jack; Kogan, Boris; Pittelli, Frank; Potrebic, Peter; Scheartz, Stuart; Simpson, Patricia; Sotessl, Michael; Spauster, Annemarie; Verdu, Sergio; 1 item
- Comparing Long Strings on a Short Systolic Array, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-026-86; Lipton, Richard J.; Lopresti, Daniel; 1 item
- Pathalias or The Care and Feeding of Relative Addresses, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-030-86; Bellovin, Steven M.; Honeyman, Peter; 1 item
- Optimization of One Bit Full Adders Embedded in Regular Structures, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-031-86; Iwano, Kazuo; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- A New Approach to Fast Control of Permutation Networks, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-032-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Youssef, Abdou; 1 item
- The Optimal Uniform Schedules of Arbitrary Static Permutations on Superposed Parallel Buses, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-033-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Crash Recovery Mechanisms for Main Storage Database Systems, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-034-86; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- The Design of Load Balancing Strategies for Distributed Systems, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-035-86; Alfonso, Rafael; 1 item
- Massive Memory Means Massive Performance, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-036-086; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Protocols for Dynamic Vote Reassignment, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-037-86; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- Three Partition Refinement Algorithms, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-038-86; Paige, Robert; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Linear Time Algorithms for Visibility and Shortest Path Problems Inside Simple Polygons, 1986; Report Report No. CS-TR-039-86; Guibas, Leo; Hershberger, John; Leven, Daniel; Sharir, Micha; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- K-Way Bitonic Sort, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-040-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Bus Partitionability and Parallel Permutations, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-041-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Array Access Bounds for Block Storage Memory Systems, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-042-861; Balasubramanian, K.; Lipton, Richard J.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Achieving High Availability in Distributed Databases, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-043-86; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; 1 item
- Soliton Phase Shifts in a Dissipative Lattice, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-044-86; Islam, Nayeem; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Garbage Collection can be Faster than Stack Allocation, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-045-86; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Optimal Parallel Sorting in a Linear Processor Array, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-046-86; Balasubramanian, K.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Reliable Distributed Database Management, 1986 August; Report No. CS-TR-047-86; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Improving Sorting Algorithms for Parallel Computers, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-048-86; Balasubramanian, K.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- One-Processor Scheduling of Tasks with Preferred Starting Times, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-49-86; Garey, Michael R.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Wilfong, Gordon T.; 1 item
- A New Approach to the Maximum Flow Problem, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-050-86; Goldberg, Andrew V.; 1 item
- Decomposition and Intersection of Simple Splinegons, 1986 August; Report No.CS-TR-051-86; Dobkin, David P.; Souvaine, Diane L.; Van Wyk, Christopher J.; 1 item
- An O (n log log n) - Time Algorithm for Triangulating Simple Polygons, 1986 July; Report No. CS-TR-052-86; Tarjan, Robert E.; Van Wyk, Christopher J.; 1 item
- A Semiring on Convex Polygons and Zero-Sum Cycle Problems, 1986 September; Report No. CS-TR-053-86; Iwano, Kazuo; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Robust Contour Tracing, 1986 September; Report No. CS-TR-054-86; Dobkin, David P.; Thurston, William P.; Wilks, Allan R.; 1 item
- Lower Bounds on the Complexity of Multidimensional Searching, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-055-86; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Increasing Availability Under Mutual Exclusion Constraints with Dynamic Vote Reassignment, 1986 November; Report No. CS-TR-056-86; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- Providing Fault Tolerance in Parallel Secondary Storage Systems, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-057-86; Balasubramanian, K.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Finding the Optimal Variable Ordering for Binary Decision Diagrams, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-058-86; Friedman, Steven J.; Supowit, Kenneth J.; 1 item
- Finding the Optimal Variable Ordering for Binary Decision Diagrams, 1986 November; Report No. CS-TR-058-86; Friedman, Steven J.; Supowit, Kenneth J.; 1 item
- Recognizing Circle Graphs in Polynomial Time, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-059-86; Gabor, Csaba P.; Hsu, Wen-Lian; 1 item
- Optimal Permutations on Superposed Parallel Buses, 1986 November; Report No. CS-TR-060-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- More Parallelism Into the Monte Carlo Solution of Partial Differential Equations, 1986 November; Report No. CS-TR-061-86; 1 item
- Linear Space Data Structures for Two Types of Range Search, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-062-86; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; 1 item
- Bitonic Sorting on Superposed Parallel Buses, 1986 November; Report No. CS-TR-063-86; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Maintaining Availability of Replicated Data in a Dynamic Failure Environment, 1986 December; Report No. CS-TR-064-86; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; 1 item
- Data Caching in an Information Retrieval System, 1986 December; Report No. CS-TR-065-86; Abad, Soraya; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Planarity Testing of Double Periodic Infinite Graphs, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-066-86; Iwano, Kazuo; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Models and Measurements of File System Performance, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-067-86; Lipton, Richard J.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Optimal Compaction of Multiple Two Component Channels under River Routing, 1986; Report No.CS-TR-068-86; Heng, F.L.; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; 1 item
- Designing Algorithms, 1986; Report No. CS-TR-069-86; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- SAGAS, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-070-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- An Improved Upper Bound for Sorting on Non-Partionable Superposed Parallel Buses, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-071-87; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Optimal Selection of Non-Partitionable Superposed Parallel Buses, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-072-87; Arden, Bruce W.; Nakatani, Toshio; 1 item
- Distributed Computing Research at Princeton-1986, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-073-87; Abbott, Robert; Alfonso, Rafael; Cova, Louis; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; Kyrimis, Kriton; Pittelli, Frank; Salem, Kenneth; Simpson, Patricia; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- Iostone: A Synthetic File System Performance Benchmark, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-074-87; Lipton, Richard J.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Performance Through Memory, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-075-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Park, Arvin; Rogers, Lawrene R.; 1 item
- Recovery in a Triple Modular Redundant Database System, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-076-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Pittelli, Frank; 1 item
- An Algorithm for Segment-Dragging and its Implementation, 1987 January; Report No. CS-TR-077-87; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Some Problems on Double Periodic Infinite Graphs, 1987 February; Report No. CS-TR-078-87; Iwano, Kazuo; 1 item
- Re-Opening Closures, 1987 February; Report No. CS-TR-079-87; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Some Thoughts on Probabilistic Databases, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-090-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Porter, Daryl; 1 item
- Update Propagation in Bakunin Data Networks, 1987; Report No.CS-TR-091-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; 1 item
- A Process Migration Implementation for a Unix System, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-092-87; Alonso, Rafael; Kyrimis, Kriton; 1 item
- Stimulating Digital Circuits with One Bit Per Wire, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-093-87; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Some Techniques for Geometric Searching with Implicit Set Representations, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-095-87; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Computing on a Free Tree Via Complexity-Preserving Mappings, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-096-87; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- A Standard ML Compiler, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-097-87; Appel, Andrew W.; MacQueen, David B.; 1 item
- Concise Specifications of Locally Optimal Code Generators, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-080-87; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- The Complexity of Cutting Complexes, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-082-87; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Guibas, Leo; 1 item
- The Processor Identity Problem, Report No. CS-TR-088-87, undated; Report No.CS-TR-088-87; Lipton, Richard J.; Park, Arvin; 1 item
- Concurrency Controls for Global Procedures in Federated Database Systems, 1987 June; Report No. CS-TR-099-87; Alonso, Rafael; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- Some Thoughts on Data Sharing Among Autonomous Cooperating Database Systems, 1987 June; Report No. CS-TR-100-87; Alonso, Rafael; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Quasi-Copies: Efficient Data Sharing for Information Retrieval Systems, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-101-87; Abad, Soraya; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- A Prototype for Research on Heterogeneous Database Systems, 1987 June; Report No. CS-TR-102-87; Alonso, Rafael; 1 item
- Amortized Analysis of Algorithms for Set Union With Backtracking, 1987 May; Report No. CS-TR-103-87; Tarjan, Robert E.; Westbrook, Jeffery; 1 item
- Algorithms for Two Bottleneck Optimization Problems, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-104-87; Gabo, Harold N.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- A Fast Parametric Maximum Flow Algorithm, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-105-87; Gallo, Giorgio; Grigoriadis, Michael D.; 1 item
- Finding Minimum-Cost Circulations By Successive Approximation, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-106-87; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Finding Minimum-Cost Circulations by Canceling Negative Cycles, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-107-87; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- A Linear Time Algorithm for Finding a Minimum Spanning Pseudoforest, 1987 July; Report No. CS-TR-108-87; Gabow, Harold N.; 1 item
- Relaxed Heaps: An Alternative to Fibonacci Heaps, 1987 July; Report No. CS-TR-109-87; Driscoll, James R.; Gabow, Harold N.; Shrairman, Ruth; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Distributed Reachability Analysis for Protocol Verification Environments, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-110-87; Aggarwal, Sudhir; Alonso, Rafael; Courcoubetis, Costas; 1 item
- Faster Scaling Algorithms for Network Problems, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-111-87; Gabow, Harold N.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- An Experimental Evaluation of Load Balancing Strategies, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-112-87; Alonso, Rafael; 1 item
- Delaunay Graphs are Almost as Good as Complete Graphs, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-113-87; Dobkin, David P.; Friedman, Steven J.; Supowit, Kenneth J.; 1 item
- Covering Minima and Lattice Point Free Convex Bodies, 1987 November; Report No. CS-TR-114-87; Kannan, Ravi; Lovasz, Laszlo; 1 item
- A Density Theorem for Purely Iterative Zero Finding Methods, 1987 November; Report No. CS-TR-115-87; Friedman, Steven J.; 1 item
- Random Polynomials and Approximate Zeros of Newton's Method, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-116-87; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- Exploiting Symmetries for Low-Cost Comparison of File Copies, 1987; Report No.CS-TR-117-87; Barbara, Daniel; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Improved Time Bounds for the Maximum Flow Problem, 1987 September; Report No. CS-TR-118-87; Ahuja, Ravindra K.; Orlin, James B.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Crash Recovery for Memory-Resident Databases, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-119-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- Sharing Jobs Among Independently Owned Processors, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-120-87; Alonso, Rafael; Cova, Louis; 1 item
- On Selecting the Second Largest with Median Tests, undated; Report No. CS-TR-121-87; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Reliable Broadcast in Networks with Nonprogrammable Servers, 1987 November; Report No. CS-TR-123-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; Lynch, Nancy; 1 item
- A Probabilistic Model for Clock Skew, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-124-87; Kugelmass, Steven D.; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Checkpointing Memory-Resident Databases, 1987 December; Report No. CS-TR-126-87; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Salem, Kenneth; 1 item
- Analysis of Algorithms for the Configuration, 1987; Report No.CS-TR-128-87; Doukas, Dimitris A.; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; 1 item
- Scheduling Real-Time Transactions, 1987; Report No. CS-TR-129-87; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Scheduling Real-Time Transactions, 1987 December; Report CS-TR-129-87; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Analysis of a Simple yet Efficient Convex Hull Algorithm, 1987 November; Report No. CS-TR-130-87; Golin, Mordecai; Sedgewick, Robert; 1 item
- Rotation Distance, Triangulations, and Hyperbolic Geometry, 1988 January; Report No. CS-TR-131-88; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Thurston, William P.; 1 item
- A Fast Las Vegas Algorithm for Triangulating a Simple Polygon, 1988 January; Report No. CS-TR-132-88; Clarkson, Kenneth; Tarjan, Robert E.; Van Wyk, Christopher J.; 1 item
- Real-time Concurrent Collection on Stock Multiprocessors, 1988 March 2; Report No. CS-TR-133-88; Appel, Andrew W.; Ellis, John R.; Li, Kai; 1 item
- Lower Bounds to Randomized Algorithms for Graph Properties, 1988 February; Report No.CS-TR-134-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- On the Complexity of Partial Order Productions, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-136-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Tight Lower Bounds for Shellsort, 1988 February; Report No. CS-TR-137-88; Sedgewick, Robert; Weiss, M.; 1 item
- On Selecting the k Largest with Median Tests, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-138-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Near Optimal Time-Space Tradeoff for Element Distinctness, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-139-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Compiling Separable Recursions, undated; Report No. CS-TR-140-88; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; 1 item
- Researching Multi-Rule Recursion Evaluation Strategies, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-141-88; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; 1 item
- Benchmarking Multi-Rule Recursion Evaluation Strategies, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-141-88; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; 1 item
- Runtime Tags Aren't Necessary, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-142-88; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Simple Generational Garbage Collection and Fast Allocation, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-143-88; Appel, Andrew W.; 1 item
- Recipes for Geometry & Numerical Analysis Part I: an Empirical Study, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-144-88; Dobkin, David P.; Silver, Deborah; 1 item
- Minimean Optimal Key Arrangements in Hash Tables, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-145-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- Scheduling Real-Time Transactions: A Performance Evaluation, undated; Report No.CS-TR-146-88; Abbott, Robert; Garcia-Molina, Hector; 1 item
- Supporting Probabilistic Data in a Relational System, 1988 February; Report No. CS-TR-147-88; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Porter, Daryl; 1 item
- An Optimal Algorithm for Intersecting Line Segments in the Plane, 1988 April; Report No. CS-TR-148-88; Chazelle, B.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; 1 item
- Algorithms for Finding a Maximum Bipartite Subgraph for Special Classes of Graphs, 1988 April; Report No. CS-TR-149-88; LaPaugh, Andrea S.; Yeh, Susan S.; 1 item
- Minimizing Expansions of Recursions, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-150-88; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; Sagiv, Yehoshua; 1 item
- Telematics Research at Princeton-1987, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-151-88; Abbott, Robert; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; Cova, Louis; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; Kyrimis, Kriton; Salem, Kenneth; Simpson, Patricia; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- An Efficient Algorithm for Finding the CSG Representation of a Simple Polygon, 1988 May; Report No. CS-TR-152-88; Dobkin, David P.; Guibas, Leo; Hershberger, John; Snoeyink, Jack; 1 item
- Searching for Empty Convex Polygons, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-153-88; Dobkin, David P.; Edelsbrunner, Herbert; Overmars, Mark H.; 1 item
- Faster Algorithms for the Shortest Path Problem, 1988 March; Report No. CS-TR-154-88; Ahuja, Ravindra K.; Melhorn, Kurt; Orlin, James B.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Tight Bounds on the Stabbing Number of Spanning Trees in Euclidean Space, 1988 May; Report No. CS-TR-155-88; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- A Fast Las Vegas Algorithm for Triangulating A Simple Polygon, 1988 May; Report No. CS-TR-157-88; Clarkson, Kenneth; Tarjan, Robert E.; Van Wyk, Christopher J.; 1 item
- Query Processing in a Heterogeneous Retrieval Network, undated; Report No.CS-TR-158-88; Simpson, Patricia; 1 item
- Multiprocessor Main Memory Transaction Processing, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-159-88; Li, Kai; Naughton, Jeffrey F.; 1 item
- Negotiating Data Access in Federated Database Systems, 1988 June; Report No. CS-TR-160-88; Alonso, Rafael; Barbara, Daniel; 1 item
- Message Ordering in a Multicast Environment, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-161-88; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Spauster, Annemarie; 1 item
- Copying Garbage Collection in the Presence of Ambiguous References, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-162-88; Appel, Andrew W.; Hanson, David R.; 1 item
- A Tight Amortized Bound for Path Reversal, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-163-88; Ginat, David; Sleator, Daniel D.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Finding Minimum-Cost Flows by Double Scaling, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-164-88; Ahuja, Ravindra K.; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Orlin, James B.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Load Balancing in Two Types of Computational Environments, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-165-88; Cova, Louis; 1 item
- Longer Bounds on the Complexity of Polytope Range Searching, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-166-88; Chazelle, B.; 1 item
- Visibility and Intersection Problems in Plane Geometry, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-167-88; Chazelle, B.; Guibas, Leo; 1 item
- Optimizing Closure Environment Representations, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-168-88; Appel, Andrew W.; Jim, Trevor T.Y.; 1 item
- Vectorized Garbage Collection, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-169-88; Appel, Andrew W.; Bendiksen, Aage; 1 item
- An Implementation of Reliable Broadcast Using an Unrealiable Multicast Facility, 1988; Report No. CS-TR-170-88; Garcia-Molina, Hector; Kogan, Boris; 1 item
- Transitive Reduction in Parallel Via Branchings, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-171-88; Gibbons, Phillip; Karp, Richard; Ramachandran, Vijaya; Soroker, Danny; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- On the Second Eigenvalue and Random Walks in Random d-Regular Graphs, 1988 August; Report No. CS-TR-172-88; Friedman, Joel; 1 item
- A Library for Infremental update of Bitamp Images, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-174-88; Dobkin, David P.; Koutsofios, Eleftherios; Pike, Rob; 1 item
- A Class of Randomized Strategies for Low-Cost Comparison of File Copies, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-176-88; Barbara, Daniel; Lipton, Richard J.; 1 item
- File Access Patterns, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-179-88; Staelin, Carl; 1 item
- PRAM: A Scalable Shared Memory, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-180-88; Lipton, Richard J.; Sandberg, Jonathan S.; 1 item
- On Straight Selection Sort, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-185-88; Chi-Chih Yao, Andrew; 1 item
- A Parallel Algorithm for Finding a Blocking Flow in an Acyclic Network, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-186-88; Goldberg, Andrew V.; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- The Efficiency of the Primal Network Simplex Algorithm for the Minimum-Cost Circulation Problem, 1988 August; Report No.CS-TR-187-88; Tarjan, Robert E.; 1 item
- Simplified Linear-Time Jordan Sorting and Polygon Clipping, 1988 July; Report No.CS-TR-189-88; Fung, Khun Yee; Nicholl, TIna M.; Tarjan, Robert E.; Van Wyk, Christopher J.; 1 item
- Throughput of Long Self-Timed Pipelines, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-190-88; Greenstreet, Mark R.; Steiglitz, Kenneth; 1 item
- Fast Allocation and Deallocation of Memory Based on Object Lifetimes, 1988; Report No.CS-TR-191-88; Hanson, David R.; 1 item